Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen Records 5141
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Montour RR (Box 233, Folder 37)
- New York Central RR (Box 233, Folder 38)
- New York, New Haven & Hartford RR (Box 233, Folder 39)
- Norfolk & Western (Box 233, Folder 40)
- New Hope & Ivyland RR (Box 233, Folder 41)
- Penn Central (Box 233, Folder 42)
- Reading RR (Box 233, Folder 43)
- Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne, Chicago RR (Box 233, Folder 44)
- Pittsburgh and Lake Erie RR (Box 233, Folder 45)
- Willsville, Addison & Galeton RR (Box 233, Folder 46)
- Western Maryland RR (Box 233, Folder 47)
- Union RR (Box 233, Folder 48)
- miscellaneous materials, ICC Dockets, etc. (Box 233, Folder 49)
- P&LERR - Discontinuance Trains -264-265-262-263-269 (Box 234, Folder 1)
- Hours of Service, March 21-26, 1966 Washington, D.C. (Box 234, Folder 2)
- Hours of Service (Box 234, Folder 3)
- Lodge 541 - J.F. Finnerty (Box 234, Folder 4)
- Nationwide Inn (Box 234, Folder 5)
- PRR - Accidents in Pennsylvania (Box 234, Folder 6)
- Monongahela Railway Company - Docket No. 6651 (Box 234, Folder 7)
- Meadville - Erie-Lackawanna RR - Lodge 207 (Box 234, Folder 8)
- Brandon, Shearer & Flaherty - Legal Services (Box 234, Folder 9)
- Thurston - NYCRR (Box 234, Folder 10)
- Railroad Bills, 1965-1967 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  1965; 1967
- Thomas F. Purnell Salary, 1966-1967 (Box 234, Folder 12)
- Sanitation Inspection (Box 234, Folder 13)
- By-Laws - Other boards (Box 234, Folder 14)
- Notes on Speeches, 1965-1968 (Box 234, Folder 15)
- Legislative Boards (Box 234, Folder 16)
- New Business (Box 234, Folder 17)
- Invitations to our state meetings (Box 234, Folder 18)
- Notes for 1967 state meeting (Box 234, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO, 1966-1967 (Box 234, Folder 20)
- Write Your Senator Program Expense (Box 234, Folder 21)
- Copy of Letters, 1965-1969 (Box 234, Folder 22)
- RLPL, 1966-1968 (Box 234, Folder 23)
- Endorsement of candidates (Box 235, Folder 1)
- Misc. letters - Flagman bill, Ohio statement on our safe crew bill (Box 235, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Resolution, 1966 (Box 235, Folder 3)
- Thomas F. Purnell - Misc. (Box 235, Folder 4)
- Misc. early Pennsylvania Legislative Board Records (Box 235, Folder 5)
- Alabama, 1939-1953 (Box 236, Folder 1)
- California (see separate series) (Box 236, Folder 2)
- Canada, 1920-1951 (Box 236, Folder 3)
- Colorado, 1949-1951 (Box 236, Folder 4)
- Delaware, 1951 (Box 236, Folder 5)
- Florida, 1947-1951 (Box 236, Folder 6)
- Georgia, 1951-1952 (Box 236, Folder 7)
- Idaho, 1952 (Box 236, Folder 8)
- Illinois, 1928-1952 (Box 236, Folder 9)
- Indiana, 1947 (Box 236, Folder 10)
- Iowa, 1949 (Box 236, Folder 11)
- Kansas, 1935-1947 (Box 236, Folder 12)
- Kentucky, 1952 (Box 236, Folder 13)
- Louisiana 1934-52 (Box 236, Folder 14)
- Maine, 1921-1951 (Box 236, Folder 15)
- Maryland, 1937-1966 (Box 236, Folder 16)
- Massachusetts, 1924-1925 (Box 236, Folder 17)
- Michigan, 1938-1949 (Box 236, Folder 18)
- Minnesota, 1949-1954 (Box 236, Folder 19)
- Mississippi, 1940-1946 (Box 236, Folder 20)
- Missouri, 1948 (Box 236, Folder 21)
- Montana, 1947-1964 (Box 236, Folder 22)
- Nevada, 1925 (Box 236, Folder 23)
- New Jersey, 1929-1966 (Box 236, Folder 24)
- New Mexico, 1930 (Box 236, Folder 25)
- New York (see separate series) (Box 236, Folder 26)
- North Carolina, 1951 (Box 236, Folder 27)
- North Dakota (Box 236, Folder 28)
- Ohio, 1931-1966 (Box 236, Folder 29-31)
- Oklahoma, 1947-1949 (Box 236, Folder 32)
- Oregon, 1949-1967 (Box 236, Folder 33)
- Pennsylvania (see separate series) (Box 236, Folder 34)
- South Dakota, 1927-1931 (Box 236, Folder 35)
- Tennessee, 1951 (Box 236, Folder 36)
- Texas, 1923-1952 (Box 236, Folder 37-38)
- Utah, 1919-1947 (Box 236, Folder 39)
- Vermont, 1921 (Box 236, Folder 40)
- Virginia, 1948-1952 (Box 236, Folder 41)
- Washington, 1947-1952 (Box 236, Folder 42)
- West Virginia, 1927-1948 (Box 236, Folder 43)
- Wisconsin, 1925-1952 (Box 236, Folder 44)
- Wyoming, 1927-1939 (Box 236, Folder 45)
- Directories of Subordinate Lodges' (Bd. Volumes), 1935-1967 (Box 237, Folder 1)
- Directories of Subordinate Lodges' (Bd. Volumes), 1935-1968 (Box 238, Folder 1)
- Directories of Subordinate Lodges' (Bd. Volumes), 1935-1969 (Box 239, Folder 1)
- Directories of Subordinate Lodges' (Bd. Volumes), 1935-1970 (Box 240, Folder 1)
- Directories of Subordinate Lodges' (Bd. Volumes), 1935-1971 (Box 241, Folder 1)
- Directories of Subordinate Lodges' (Bd. Volumes), 1935-1972 (Box 242, Folder 1)
- Constitutions, 1875-1969 (Box 243, Folder 1)
- Railroad Booklets - re rules, schedules, rates, operating manuals, lists of delegates, rituals, convention booklets, and miscellaneous (Box 244, Folder 1)
- Railroad Booklets - re rules, schedules, rates, operating manuals, lists of delegates, rituals, convention booklets, and miscellaneous (Box 245, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Railroad Publications (Box 245.1, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Railroad Publications, Photographs, and Wills of Timothy and Mollie Shea (Box 245.2, Folder 1)
- Monthly Bulletin of the BLF&E (Box 245.3, Folder 1)
- Monthly Bulletin of the BLF&E (Box 245.4, Folder 1)
- State of Wisconsin, Circuit Court. Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company vs. Benson LaFollette, et al and BLF&E and BRT (Box 246, Folder 1)
  Case #115-458 1966, Transcripts, 18 vols. and exhibits.
- State of Wisconsin, Circuit Court. Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company vs. Benson LaFollette, et al and BLF&E and BRT (Box 247, Folder 1)
- State of Wisconsin, Circuit Court. Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company vs. Benson LaFollette, et al and BLF&E and BRT (Box 248, Folder 1)
- State of Wisconsin, Circuit Court. Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company vs. Benson LaFollette, et al and BLF&E and BRT (Box 249, Folder 1)
- In the U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals for the 7th District, 1927-1967 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  1927-Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co, vs. BLF&E #4009; In the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia, Circuit Court, BLF&E Appellant vs. Bangor and Aroostook Railroad Co., et al and the Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway Co., et al
- In the U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals for the 7th District, 1927-1967 (Box 251, Folder 1)
- Conductor's Graduated Rates Case, 1954, Exhibits. Engineers' 30% Wage Case, 1954, Exhibits. (Box 252, Folder 1)
- Engineers-Firemen-Switchmen, 1948 Rules Case, Exhibits. (Box 253, Folder 1)
- Rules Movement, 1959 and Miscellaneous Exhibits, Awards, Cases. (Box 254, Folder 1)
- Rules Movement, 1959 and Miscellaneous Exhibits, Awards, Cases. (Box 255, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Exhibits, 1927-1967 (Box 256, Folder 1)
  Publications, Cases, Briefs; Stenographer's Minutes of Report of Conference of Committee of Managers of Eastern Railroads, 6 vols., 1927; Minutes of Meetings Held Between National Conference Committee of the Railways and the BLE, BLF&E, ORC, BRT, New York
- Miscellaneous Exhibits, 1942-1949 (Box 257, Folder 1)
  Jt. Concerted Wage Movement, Exhibits, 1942?; 1947 Wage and Rule Issue, Exhibits; Second Diesel Case, Exhibits, 1949.
- Miscellaneous Exhibits and related documents. (Box 258, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous U.S. Supreme Court and Court of Appeals, Cases (Box 258.1, Folder 1)
- Agreements, 1885-1961 (Box 259, Folder 1)
- Booklets re rules, schedules, rates, and manuals. (Box 260, Folder 1)
- Booklets re rules, schedules, rates, and manuals. (Box 261, Folder 1)
- General Grievance Committee. (Box 262, Folder 1)
- Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company (Box 263, Folder 15)
- Speeches - H.E. Gilbert - Pres. BLF&E, 1960 (Box 263, Folder 2)
- Speeches - H.E. Gilbert - Pres. BLF&E (Box 263, Folder 3)
- Mileage (Box 263, Folder 4)
- Mileage [cont.] (Box 263, Folder 5)
- Delray, Mich. - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 263, Folder 6)
- BLF&E - Peoria, Ill., 1915 (Box 263, Folder 7)
- BLF&E - Peoria, Ill. [cont.], 1915 (Box 263, Folder 8)
- BLF&E - Peoria, Ill. [cont.], 1915 (Box 263, Folder 9)
- BLF&E - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 263, Folder 10)
- General Grievance Committee - BLF&E, 1914-1915 (Box 263, Folder 11)
- Interpretation of Tariffs, 1920 (Box 263, Folder 12)
- Samuel C. Phillips, 1963 (Box 263, Folder 14)
- Report of the Board of Directors of the BLF&E, 1967 (Box 263, Folder 22)
- BLF&E Instruction Pamphlets (Box 263, Folder 16)
- BLF&E Instruction Pamphlets (Box 263, Folder 17)
- H.E. Gilbert - Personal, 1957 (Box 263, Folder 18)
- J.H. Neely - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 263, Folder 19)
- Responsibilities of a local chairman (Box 263, Folder 20)
- Proceedings, Testimony and Evidence: Special Trial Comm., 1908 (Box 263, Folder 21)
- Agreement for Protection of Employes (Box 263, Folder 23)
- Collective Bargaining Re Concerted Movement Procedure (Box 263, Folder 24)
- Inside Story of the Settlement of the Railroad Strike of May 25, 1946 (Box 263, Folder 25)
- Minutes of Meeting of General Policy Committee - March 9, 1964 (Box 263, Folder 26)
- Trial of F.W. DeArment and R.R. Wright, 1933 (Box 263, Folder 27)
- UTU - Railroad drawings, 1970 (Box 263, Folder 28)
- BLF&E - Correspondence, 1917-1968 (Box 263, Folder 13)
- Speeches - H.E. Gilbert - Pres. BLF&E, 1954 (Box 263, Folder 1)
- In the Appellate Court.. February Term A.D. 1894 (Box 264, Folder 7)
- Officials and the B. of L.E. Committees [part of title page ripped off], 1907 (Box 264, Folder 6)
- Eastern Concerted Wage Movement, 1912-1913 (Box 264, Folder 5)
- Arbitration Proceedings between the C. & W. I.R.R. Co. and the Belt Ry. Co. and the B.L.E. Vol. II, 1913 (Box 264, Folder 4)
- General Order NO. 27 with Supplements and Interpretations, 1920 (Box 264, Folder 3)
- Wabash Railroad Injunction Case, 1903 (Box 264, Folder 2)
- Proceedings of the U.S. Railroad Labor Board - May 4 to May 6, 1920 (Box 264, Folder 1)
- Monthly Report of V.P. and Act. V.P., 1967 (Box 265, Folder 7)
- Monthly Report of V.P. and Act. V.P., 1966 (Box 265, Folder 6)
- Monthly Report of V.P. and Act. V.P., 1965 (Box 265, Folder 5)
- Semi-Annual Report - G.S. & T., 1959-1962 (Box 265, Folder 4)
- Quarterly Report - G.S. & T., 1953-1958 (Box 265, Folder 3)
- Quarterly Report - G.S. & T., 1948-1952 (Box 265, Folder 2)
- War Service Information (Box 265, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen & Enginemen Actuarial Reports: 1920 / by Sidney H. Pipe, 1930 (Box 266, Folder 10)
- Souvenir B of L F & E: 1922 (3 copies); 1925 (2 copies) -- Rituel de la Fraternite des Ingenieurs et Chauffeurs de Locomotives, 1922-1925 (Box 266, Folder 2)
- Program Fiftieth Anniversary. 1873-1923; Souvenir B. of L. F. & E. 1925, 1873-1925 (Box 266, Folder 3)
- Monthly Record of Membership (Box 266, Folder 4)
- B L F & E - Cleveland, Ohio: Correspondence and Misc. (Box 266, Folder 5)
- Chicago Joint Agreement Rulings (Box 266, Folder 6)
- Apprenticeship Training (Box 266, Folder 7)
- Report of the Board of Directors - June 5, 1916-Jan. 7, 1919; Ritual B. of L.F. of E. (2 copies), 1916-1919 (Box 266, Folder 1)
- Grand Lodge Officers, General Organizers, General Chairman - BLF & E (Box 266, Folder 9)
- Program - Fiftieth Anniversary. (1873-1923); Misc. (Box 266, Folder 17)
- H.E. Gilbert (Box 266, Folder 11)
- 1876-March 10, 1911, 1876-1911 (Box 266, Folder 12)
- Souvenir B of LF & # (1922) (Box 266, Folder 13)
- Index to Monthly Bulletins, 1935 (Box 266, Folder 14)
- B of LF & E Monthly Bulletins, 1949 (Box 266, Folder 15)
- Minutes of General Comm. Of B of LF & E, 1955 (Box 266, Folder 16)
- Bro. of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen - Financial Statements and Report, Aug. 31, 1953 (Box 266, Folder 8)
- BLFE Contains: BLF&E Broadside, Oct. 1930, Albany, NY (Box 268)
- BLFE Drawings and posters, Staufer drawing (Box 269)